Hola.
Sorry.
I spoiled your lovely evening,
Cinderella….
That’s all right.
You know,
I wouldn't call a whole day
with Mason “lovely”.
I thought things were going
okay between you two.
It's impossible.
Grandpa.
I think
Mason has done his part.
The company is stronger
than ever and...
Please.
Give me your blessing for a divorce.
He's not even a part of our family.
I'm begging you.
No.
I won't allow it.
I don't understand.
Why are you doing all this?
Yes.
He’s probably good
at business, but
he's a stranger.
He is not the right choice for me.
It's not right for all of us.
I didn't choose him
for his business skills.
Then what for?
Don't you remember?
What?
Back when your parents were friends,
he often visited the mansion.
I kept an eye on him.
Mason was different
from other Powells.
Noble.
Strong.
He didn't care what others thought.
He always stood up for...
I'd say “good”.
But that sounds like a fairy tale.
Let's just call it justice.